Guide to the Radio TV Reports Infomercial Collection, 1990-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Radio TV Reports Infomercial collection 1990-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Radio TV Reports Inc.
12.0 linear feet Extent: 149 Items
Broadcast service company that records, transcribes and monitors radio and television programming. Collection spans the years 1990-1996 and consists of over 800 as-broadcast televised infomercials and public service programs recorded on VHS. Topics include direct marketing for health and beauty aids, kitchen appliances, exercise equipment, wealth management and collectible items. Celebrities featured as spokespersons include Cher, Joe Theisman, Richard Simmons and Victoria Jackson. Services represented include health and insurance providers and nonprofit organizations such as the New Jersey Education Association. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
radiotvinfomercials
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Radio TV Reports Infomercial Collection were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2012.
Collection Overview
Collection spans the years 1990-1996 and consists of over 800 as-broadcast televised infomercials and public service programs recorded on VHS. Topics include direct marketing for health and beauty aids, kitchen appliances, exercise equipment, wealth management and collectible items. Celebrities featured as spokespersons include Cher, Joe Theisman, Richard Simmons and Victoria Jackson. Services represented include health and insurance providers and nonprofit organizations such as the New Jersey Education Association.
Collection Arrangement
VHS tapes have been numbered. Collection arranged numerically. Gaps in the numbering represent tapes not received with the collection.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Radio TV Reports Inc; New Jersey Education Association; Cher, 1946-; Jackson, Victoria; Simmons, Richard; Theisman, Joe; Advertising, Public service; Direct marketing; Infomercials; Television advertising; Videotapes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related material may also be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Adrienne Cohen Papers
John Stevenson Papers
Lester Wunderman Papers
Wunderman Archives
Detailed Description of Collection
- Original Tapes, 1990-1996
  - Tape 1 (Box 1)
    - Mega Memory Photographic Memory. FNN-TV. 1990 May 31. 3:00 AM.
    - $50,000 Opportunity Showcase--Entrepreneurs. FNN-TV. 1990 May 313:30 AM.
    - Howard Ruff--Achieve Prosperity in the 90s. FNN-TV. 1990 May 314:00 AM.
    - Fran Tarkenton--Personal Achievement. FNN-TV. 1990 May 314:30 AM.
  - Tape 2
    - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 2. 6:00 AM.
    - Incredible Breakthrough--Liquid Lustre. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 2. 6:30 AM.
    - Unlocking the Mystery of Marriage. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 2. 7:00 AM.
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 2. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 3
    - Soloflex. WNBC-TV. 1990 June 2. 1:00 PM.
  - Tape 4
    - Richard Simmons--Deal a Meal. WWOR-TV1990 June2. 8:00 AM.
    - Harvey's Smart Kitchen--Electric Kitchen. WWOR-TV1990 June2. 8:30 AM.
    - Vikki Lamotia--You Can Look Younger. WWOR-TV1990 June2. 9:00 AM.
    - Making Life Easier with Dave Clark--Clark Snackmaster. WWOR-TV1990 June2. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 5
    - Amazing Discoveries--Astonish Cleaner. WNYW-TV. 1990 June3. 10:00 AM.
    - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Daily Maintenance. WNYW-TV. 1990 June3. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 6
    - Joe Theisman 30 Minute Workout. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 3. 12:00 AM.
  - Tape 7
    - Financial Freedom. LIF-TV. 1990 June 5. 3:00 AM.
  - Tape 8
    - Richard Simmons--Deal a Meal. Lifetime. 1990 Mar. 21. 5:30 AM.
    - Gary Kakson--How to Get a Second Paycheck. Lifetime. 1990 Mar. 21. 6:00 AM.
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s. Lifetime. 1990 Mar. 21. 6:30 AM.
  - Tape 9
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s. Lifetime. 1990 Mar. 22. 1:00 AM.
    - Amazing Discovery--Natural White. Lifetime. 1990 Mar. 22. 1:30 AM.
    - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate. Lifetime. 1990 Mar. 22. 2:00 AM.
    - Susan Purcell--Cash for the Asking. Lifetime. 1990 Mar. 22. 2:30 AM.
  - Tape 10
    - Cashing in on the Cashless Society. LIF-TV. 1990 June 5. 1:30 AM.
    - Solid Gold Rock and Roll. LIF-TV. 1990 June 5. 2:00 AM.
    - Susan Purcell--Cash for the Asking. LIF-TV. 1990 June 5. 2:30 AM.
  - Tape 11
    - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Great Wok of China. Family Channel. 1990 June 6. 3:00 AM.
    - Joe McKenzie Breakthroughs--Hobei Kitchen Utensil. Family Channel. 1990 June 6. 3:30 AM.
    - Kevin Trudeau--Memory Mega. Family Channel. 1990 June 6. 4:00 AM.
    - Amazing Discovery--Astonish Cleaner. Family Channel. 1990 June 6. 4:30 AM.
  - Tape 12
    - Michael Reed--Subliminal Communications. USA1990 June 8. 6:00 AM.
    - Soloflex (female) Male-Dance. USA1990 June 8. 6:30 AM.
  - Tape 13
    - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Great Wok of China. WNYW-TV. 1990 June 3. 9:00 AM.
    - Amazing Discovery--Natural White. WNYW-TV. 1990 June 3. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 14
    - Better Ways to Better Grades (Where There Is a Will There Is an A). TBS. 1990 June 3. 12:00 AM.
    - Unlocking the Mystery of Marriage. TBS. 1990 June 3. 12:30 AM.
    - Is There Love After Marriage--Dave Clark. TBS. 1990 June 3. 1:00 AM.
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s. TBS. 1990 June 3. 1:30 AM.
  - Tape 15
    - JS&A, The Making of a Commercial--Blocker Sunglasses. WPIX-TV. 1990 June 9. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 16
    - Kitchen Mate. WNYW-TV. 1990 June 9. 6:00 AM.
    - Stain-A-Rator. WNYW-TV. 1990 June 9. 6:30 AM.
    - The World Tomorrow. WNYW-TV. 1990 June 9. 7:00 AM.
    - Auri--John Ritter. WNYW-TV. 1990 June 9. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 17
    - Craftmatic Bed--Better Sleep. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 9. 12:30 AM.
  - Tape 18
    - Better Ways to Better Grades (Where There Is a Will There Is an A)--John Ritter. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 9. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 19
    - Regina Housekeeper Plus. WVTV-TV. 1990 June 10. 10:00 AM.
  - Tape 20
    - Stain-A-Rator. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 9. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 21
    - Lifesigns Stop Smoking featuring E.L. Marshall, Florence Henderson. WNYW-TV. 1990 June 16. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 22
    - Command Performance Relationship between You and Your Dog--Bruce Weitz. WPGH-TV. 1990 June 16. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 23
    - Now You're Cooking--Super Server featuring Christopher Hewett. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 16. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 24
    - Nike. TBS. 1990 June 17. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 25
    - Nike. TBS. 1990 June 17. 12:00 AM.
  - Tape 26
    - Hair Club for Men featuring Sy Sperling. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 16. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 27
    - Amazing Discovery--Natural White. Family Channel. 1990 Sept. 28. 3:30 AM.
    - Flowbee Vacuum Haircut. Family Channel. 1990 Sept. 28. 4:00 AM.
    - Being Your Own Boss. Family Channel. 1990 Sept. 28. 4:30 AM.
    - Amazing Micro Diet--Kathy Lee Crosby. Family Channel. 1990 Sept. 28. 5:00 AM.
  - Tape 28
    - Cuisine International Presents The Great Wall of China. WWOR-TV. 1990 June 24. 12:00 AM.
  - Tape 29
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s. WWOR-TV. 1990 Sept. 22. 8:00 AM.
    - Inside Secrets--Magic White. WWOR-TV. 1990 Sept. 22. 8:30 AM.
    - Personal Power--Anthony Robbins. WWOR-TV. 1990 Sept. 22. 9:00 AM.
    - Entrepreneur--Be Your Own Boss. WWOR-TV. 1990 Sept. 22. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 30
    - Amazing Micro Diet--Kathy Lee Crosby. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 8:00 AM.
    - Incredible Breakthrough--Sisan Iron. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 8:30 AM.
    - Kathy Smith Diet--Fat Burning System. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 9:00 AM.
    - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 31 (Box 2)
    - This is the NFL. NBC-TV.1991 Jan. 13. 12:00 PM.
    - Where There Is a Will There Is an A--John Ritter. NBC-TV.1991 Jan. 13. 12:30 PM.
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s. NBC-TV.1991 Jan. 13. 1:00 PM.
    - Sisan Steam Iron--Incredible Breakthrough featuring Linda Michaels. NBC-TV.1991 Jan. 13. 1:30 PM.
  - Tape 32
    - Beauty Breakthroughs--Amazing Micro Diet. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 1. 10:00 AM.
    - Health Innovations--When You're Ready to Quit. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 1. 10:30 AM.
    - Sulit-T-Go Age-Free Skin. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 1. 11:00 AM.
    - Inside Secrets--Magic White featuring Richard Bey. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 1. 11:30 AM.
  - Tape 35
    - Hair Club for Men featuring Sy Sperling. WNBC-TV. 1991 Jan. 13. 12:17 AM.
    - Brain Supercharger--Millionaire's Mind. WNBC-TV. 1991 Jan. 13. 12:47 AM.
  - Tape 36
    - The Love Phone--Jessica Hahn. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 12:30 AM.
    - When You're Ready to Quit Smoking. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 1:00 AM.
    - The Weight Loss Revolution--Kathy Lee Crosby. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 1:30 AM.
  - Tape 37
    - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate. WNYW-TV. 1991Jan. 6. 8:30 AM.
    - Weight Loss Revolution--Amazing Micro Diet. WNYW-TV. 1991Jan. 6. 9:00 AM.
    - Anushka--Erin Gray Straight Talk. WNYW-TV. 1991Jan. 6. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 38
    - Incredible Breakthrough--The Punch Connection (Craft for the Family). WPIX-TV. 1991 Jan. 21. 7:00 AM.
    - St. Go Skin Care System. WPIX-TV. 1991 Jan. 21. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 39
    - Now You're Cooking--Super Snacker. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 6. 12:30 AM.
    - Diet Disc Program--HerbaLife. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 6. 1:00 AM.
    - Financial Freedom with John Davidson. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 6. 1:30 AM.
  - Tape 40
    - Sisan Steam Iron--Incredible Breakthrough. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 12. 8:00 AM.
    - Neutra Plak--Instant White. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 12. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 41
    - The Miracle Blade. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 6:00 AM.
    - The Weight Loss Revolution--Kathy Lee Crosby. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 6:30 AM.
    - The Power Play--Richard Ames. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 7:00 AM.
    - Health Innovations--When You're Ready to Quit. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 5. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 42
    - Snak Master--Making Life Easier. WNYW-TV. 1991Jan. 19. 8:30 AM.
    - Fat Burning System--Kathy Smith. WNYW-TV. 1991Jan. 19. 9:00 AM.
    - Incredible Breakthrough--Sisan Iron. WNYW-TV. 1991Jan. 19. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 43
    - Weight Loss Revolution--Amazing Micro Diet. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 19. 8:00 AM.
    - Sisan Iron--Incredible Breakthrough. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 19. 8:30 AM.
    - Fit One 20-Minute Workout. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 19. 9:00 AM.
    - Arnold's Gourmet Kitchen--Kitchenmate. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 19. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 44
    - Jet Steam Oven--American Harvest. KTMA-TV Minneapolis. 1991 Jan. 13. 3:30 PM.
  - Tape 45
    - Incredible Breakthrough--Turro Iron. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 26. 10:00 AM.
    - Amazing Micro Diet--Kathy Lee Crosby. WWOR-TV. 1991 Jan. 26. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 46
    - The Good Life--Getting Yours. WNYW-TV. 1991 Jan. 27. 10:00 AM.
    - Blu Blockers Sunglasses. WNYW-TV. 1991 Jan. 27. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 47
    - How to Make 1,000 a Day--The Trustee Game. WPIX-TV. 1991 Jan. 26. 7:00 AM.
    - How to Get a Second Paycheck--Hawaiian Style. WPIX-TV. 1991 Jan. 26. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 48
    - Sisan Iron--Synchronal. WNYW-TV. 1991 Jan. 27. 8:30 AM.
    - Anushka--Erin Gray Straight Talk. WNYW-TV. 1991 Jan. 27. 9:00 AM.
    - Soloflex--Family Kid Soccer. WNYW-TV. 1991 Jan. 27. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 49
    - Fat Burning System--Kathy Smith. WNYW-TV. 1991 Feb. 3. 10:00 AM.
    - Retinoid Regimen II--War Against Wrinkles with Juliet Prowse. WNYW-TV. 1991 Feb. 3. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 50
    - Hair Club for Men. WNBC-TV. 1991 Feb. 3. 12:00 PM.
    - Deal a Meal USA. WNBC-TV. 1991 Feb. 3. 12:30 PM.
  - Tape 51
    - You Can Look Younger--Vickki LaMotta and Lee Meriwether. WWOR-TV. Undated. 8:00 AM.
    - Personal Power--Michael O'Brien. WWOR-TV. Undated. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 52
    - Tom Vu--Secrets of Success (1-hour). NBC-TV.1991 Feb. 17. 12:00 PM.
  - Tape 53
    - Magic White--Richard Bey. WWOR-TV. 1991 Feb. 17. 12:00 PM.
    - Turbo Iron. WWOR-TV. 1991 Feb. 17. 12:30 PM.
    - HerbaLife. WWOR-TV. 1991 Feb. 17. 1:00 PM.
  - Tape 54
    - Blu Blockers Sunglasses. WPIX-TV. 1991 Feb. 23. 7:00 AM.
    - Human Calculator--Scott Plansford. WPIX-TV. 1991 Feb. 23. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 55
    - Sisan Iron. WPIX-TV. 1991 Feb. 23. 8:00 AM.
    - Neutra Plak--Instant White--Judi Barton. WPIX-TV. 1991 Feb. 23. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 56
    - Rock and Roll Era--Time Life Music. WPIX-TV. 1991 Mar. 2. 7:00 AM.
    - Human Calculator--Scott Plansford. WPIX-TV. 1991 Mar. 2. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 57
    - Fit One Fitness Quest. WNYW-TV. 1991 Mar. 3. 9:00 AM.
    - A Second Paycheck. WNYW-TV. 1991 Mar. 3. 9:30 AM.
    - War Against Wrinkles. WNYW-TV. 1991 Mar. 3. 10:00 AM.
  - Tape 58
    - Blu Blockers Sunglasses. WPIX-TV. 1991 Mar. 9. 7:00 AM.
    - Take 30 30-Minute Workout with Joe Theisman, S. Easton, Dave Scott. WPIX-TV. 1991 Mar. 9. 7:30 AM.
    - Deal a Meal USA. WPIX-TV. 1991 Mar. 9. 8:00 AM.
    - Where There Is a Will There Is an A--John Ritter. WPIX-TV. 1991 Mar. 9. 8:30 AM.
  - Tape 59
    - Fitness Quest--Abdominizer. WWOR-TV. 1991 Mar. 23. 6:00 AM.
    - Power Bands--Joe Namath. WWOR-TV. 1991 Mar. 23. 6:30 AM.
    - Models Choice Collection--S-T-Go. WWOR-TV. 1991 Mar. 23. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 60
    - Brain Supercharger--Millionaire's Mind. WNBC-TV. 1991 Mar. 30. 6:30 AM.
    - Will Your Kid Make the Grade--Michael Landon. WNBC-TV. 1991 Mar. 30. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 61
    - Merve Wrinkle Cream--The All America Miracle Search. WWOR-TV. 1991 Apr. 12. 12:00 AM.
  - Tape 62
    - Freedom from Pain--Therapy Plus. WPIX-TV. 1991 Apr. 27. 7:30 AM.
    - Human Calculator--Scott Plansford. WPIX-TV. 1991 Apr. 27. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 63 (Box 3)
    - The Early 90s Dog Training--Bruce Weitz. Family Channel. 1991 May 9. 2:00 AM.
    - The Power Steamer--Mike Levi. Family Channel. 1991 May 9. 2:30 AM.
    - Soloflex--Football Tennis. Family Channel. 1991 May 9. 3:00 AM.
    - Molecular Medicine--Vitamin Diet MDR Fitness. Family Channel. 1991 May 9. 3:30 AM.
  - Tape 64
    - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies. WWOR-TV. 1991 May 11. 10:00 AM.
    - The Juiceman--Richard Bey. WWOR-TV. 1991 May 11. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 65
    - Fantasy for Sale--World Tomorrow. WPIX-TV. 1991 July 13. 6:00 AM.
    - The Millionaire School. WPIX-TV. 1991 July 13. 6:30 AM.
  - Tape 67
    - Deal a Meal--Richard Simmons. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 13. 8:00 AM.
    - Celeste Caruso Hairsetter--Anna Stuart. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 13. 8:30 AM.
    - The Greatest Animated Bible Stories. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 13. 9:00 AM.
  - Tape 68
    - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 20. 10:00 AM.
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s with Meredith Baxter-Bernie, Ali McGraw. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 20. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 69
    - Celeste Caruso Hairsetter--Anna Stuart. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 20. 8:30 AM.
    - War Against Wrinkles. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 20. 9:00 AM.
  - Tape 70
    - Game of Love--Jessica Hahn. WWOR-TV. 1991 June 8. 12:30 AM.
    - Will Your Kid Make the Grade--Michael Landon. WWOR-TV. 1991 June 8. 1:00 AM.
    - Personal Power--Anthony Robbins. WWOR-TV. 1991 June 8. 1:30 AM.
  - Tape 71
    - Beauty Breakthrough II--Victoria Jackson. WWOR-TV. 1991 Aug. 17. 8:00 AM.
    - Wealth Without Risk--Charles Givens. WWOR-TV. 1991 Aug. 17. 8:30 AM.
    - Family Entertainment--The Miracle of Jesus. WWOR-TV. 1991 Aug. 17. 9:00 AM.
    - This is Club Med--Paradise Found. WWOR-TV. 1991 Aug. 17. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 72
    - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 27. 8:00 AM.
    - Personal Power--Robert Bey, Fran Tarkenton. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 27. 8:30 AM.
    - Family Entertainment--Bible. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 27. 9:00 AM.
    - Freedom from Pain--Therapy Plus. WWOR-TV. 1991 July 27. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 73
    - Blu Blockers Sunglasses--Rapper. WPIX-TV. 1991 Aug. 3. 8:00 AM.
  - Tape 74
    - Say Goodbye to Wrinkles--Vickki LaMotta, Lyle Wagganer. WWOR-TV. 1991 Sept. 21. 9:00 AM.
    - Fit One Fitness Quest. WWOR-TV. 1991 Sept. 21. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 75
    - Hooked on Phonics--Chad Murdock. WPIX-TV. 1991 Sept. 21. 6:30 AM.
    - How to Be a Millionaire--The Millionaire School with Dave Del Dotto. WPIX-TV. 1991 Sept. 21. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 76
    - Principal Secrets--Victoria Principal. WWOR-TV. 1991 Aug. 24. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 77
    - Volvo Cars San Diego. KLSI-TV. 1991 Sept. 29. 1:00 AM.
  - Tape 78
    - Fit One Fitness Quest. WWOR-TV. 1991 Sept. 7. 6:00 AM.
    - When You're Ready to Quit Smoking. WWOR-TV. 1991 Sept. 7. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 79
    - Secrets of the Rich and Successful--Jay McCorkle. WNYW-TV. 1991 Sept. 14. 4:30 PM.
  - Tape 80
    - Healing a Broken Planet. WPIX-TV. 1991 Oct. 5. 6:00 AM.
    - Hooked on Phonics--Chad Murdock. WPIX-TV. 1991 Oct. 5. 6:30 AM.
    - Lazervision Pinhole Glasses. WPIX-TV. 1991 Oct. 5. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 81
    - Hooked on Phonics--Chad Murdock. WPIX-TV. 1991 Nov. 2. 6:30 AM.
    - Your Love in Action--Jame Robeson Ministries with Glen Campbell. WPIX-TV. 1991 Nov. 2. 7:00 AM.
    - Sani Safe Cutlery--Dexter Russell. WPIX-TV. 1991 Nov. 2. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 82
    - Miracle Blade--Wayne Harvey. WNBC-TV. 1991 Oct. 12. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 83
    - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthrough for the 90s with Meredith Baxter-Bernie. WWOR-TV. 1991 Oct. 19. 8:00 AM.
    - Shealy Relaxmate Glasses--Dick Van Patten. WWOR-TV. 1991 Oct. 19. 8:30 AM.
    - Freedom from Pain--Therapy Plus. WWOR-TV. 1991 Oct. 19. 9:00 AM.
    - Fit One--Trailer, Bus, Skiing. WWOR-TV. 1991 Oct. 19. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 84
    - Relationships Today--Dick Clark. WWOR-TV. 1991 Oct. 19. 6:30 AM.
    - The Juiceman--Richard Bey. WWOR-TV. 1991 Oct. 19. 7:00 AM.
    - Make-Over Magic--Michael Marone. WWOR-TV. 1991 Oct. 19. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 85
    - Alpha-Netics Speed Reading--Owen Skousen. Family Channel. 1991 Oct. 24. 2:00 AM.
    - Human Calculator--Scott Plansford. Family Channel. 1991 Oct. 24. 2:30 AM.
    - Personal Power--Anthony Robbins, Fran Tarkenton. Family Channel. 1991 Oct. 24. 3:00 AM.
    - Where There Is a Will There Is an A--John Ritter. Family Channel. 1991 Oct. 24. 3:30 AM.
  - Tape 86
    - Smart Buyers Network--Hassle Free Way to Buy a Car. WNBC-TV. 1991 Nov. 9. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 87
    - Cher's Focus on Beauty--Lori's Hair Care. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 9. 10:00 AM.
    - Deal a Meal. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 9. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 88
    - Blu Blocker Sunglasses--Rapper. WPIX-TV. 1991 Nov. 23. 8:00 AM.
    - The Juiceman--Richard Bey. WPIX-TV. 1991 Nov. 23. 8:30 AM.
    - Juice Tiger Machine--Jack LaLane. WPIX-TV. 1991 Nov. 23. 9:00 AM.
  - Tape 89
    - Star Charts--What's in the Stars for You. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 6:00 AM.
    - Relationships Today--Is there Love After Marriage. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 6:30 AM.
    - Inside Track to Fitness--Bob Seagram, Mark Spitz. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 7:00 AM.
    - The Juiceman--John Kordich. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 90
    - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 8:00 AM.
    - Personal Power (Changes in Your Life)--Anthony Robbins. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 8:30 AM.
    - Galloping Gourmet--Perfectionnaire Oven. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 9:00 AM.
    - Fit One--Road, Bus, Skiing. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 91
    - Oster Kitchen Center (appliances)--Graham Kerr. WWOR-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 92
    - Star Charts--Astrological Guide. WWOR-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 6:00 AM.
    - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies. WWOR-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 6:30 AM.
    - Today's Family--Modern Medication with Dr. Joyce Brothers. WWOR-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 7:00 AM.
    - Fit One--Trailer, Bus, Skiing. WWOR-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 93
    - Hooked on Phonics--Chad Murdock. WPIX-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 7:00 AM.
    - Ronco Incredible Inventions (Food Processor). WPIX-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 94 (Box 4)
    - Jane Fonda Lower Body System. WNBC-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 6:00 AM.
    - Blue Tango Lingerie. WNBC-TV. 1991 Dec. 7. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 95
    - Jane Fonda Lower Body System. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 2. 6:00 AM.
    - Deal a Meal--Surprise Visit. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 2. 6:30 AM.
    - Making Money--Don LaPrade. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 2. 7:00 AM.
    - The Juiceman. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 2. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 96
    - Hair Club for Men. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 16. 8:30 AM.
    - Fit One--Cross-country Skiing. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 16. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 97
    - The Original 40-Food Robot Processor. WNBC-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 98
    - Deal a Meal--Pounds Away Plane. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 10:00 AM.
    - Will Your Kid Make the Grade--Michael Landon. WWOR-TV. 1991 Nov. 30. 10:30 AM.
  - Tape 99
    - Best of Your Hit Parade--Steve Allen Songs from the 40s and 50s. WPIX-TV. 1991 Dec. 14. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 100
    - Blu Blocker. WPIX-TV. 1991 Dec. 14. No time.
    - The Juiceman. WPIX-TV. 1991 Dec. 14. No time.
    - Colorcote 2000--Car Care Polish. WPIX-TV. 1991 Dec. 14. 9:00 AM.
    - Oster Kitchen Center--Food processor. WPIX-TV. 1991 Dec. 14. 9:30 AM.
  - Tape 101
    - Jane Fonda Lower Body System. WNBC-TV. 1991 Dec. 28. 6:00 AM.
    - Nordic Flex Gold exercise machine. WNBC-TV. 1991 Dec. 28. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 102
    - Nordic Track Ski Machine--Mark Spitz, B. Seagram. WWOR-TV. 1991 Dec. 29. 7:00 AM.
    - Slim and Easy Mouth Spray (for weight control)--Ruby Lee. WWOR-TV. 1991 Dec. 29. 7:30 AM.
  - Tape 103
    - Jane Fonda Workout--The Next Step. WNBC-TV. 1992 Jan. 4. No time.
    - St. Go Age Free Skin--Beverly Sills. WNBC-TV. 1992 Jan. 4. No time.
    - Milin Method--No Excuses Money Making System. WNBC-TV. 1992 Jan. 4. 7:00 AM.
  - Tape 104
    - Personal Power--Anthony Robbins. WWOR-TV. 1992 Jan. 4. No time.
    - This is Club Med--Vacations. WWOR-TV. 1992 Jan. 4. 9:00 AM.
    - Fit One--Cross-country Skiing. WWOR-TV. 1992 Jan. 4. No time.
  - Tape 106
    - Saturn Automobile. Channel 10. 1991 Apr. 18. 11:05 PM.
  - Tape 107
    - Golf Breakthrough for the 90s--Pat Summerall and Wally Armstrong. WWOR-TV. 1992 Feb. 29. 8:00 AM.
    - The Ultimate Squeeze Juice Machine--Robin Thomas, Molly Fox, Dr. Richard Backrach. 1992 Feb. 29. 8:30AM.
  - Tape 108
    - Blu Blockers sunglasses. WPIX-TV. 1992 Feb. 15. 8:00 AM.
    - The Juiceman. WPIX-TV. 1992 Feb. 15. 8:30 AM.
    - Oster Kitchen Center--Graham Kerr juice machine. WPIX-TV. 1992 Feb. 15. 9:00 AM.
    - The Juice Tiger--Jack LaLane. WPIX-TV. 1992 Feb. 15. 9:30AM.
  - Tape 109
    - Nordic Flex Gold exercise machine. WWOR-TV. 1992 Feb. 8. 9:00 AM.
  - Tape 110
    - Hair Club for Men--Strand by Strand System, Cures for thinning and loss of hair. WWOR-TV. 1992 Feb. 15. 12:30 PM.
  - Tape 111
    - Colorcote 2000--Car Care Polish. WPIX-TV. 1992 Feb. 8. 8:30AM.
    - How to Train Your Dog in only 10 Minutes a Day--Gary Cochran. WPIX-TV. 1992 Feb. 8. 9:00AM.
  - Tape 112
    - Target---Season with Ginger and Spice; McCoy Media. No station. Undated. No time.
  - Tape 113
    - Nordic Track--The Fit One. WWOR-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 6:00 AM.
    - Golf Breakthrough for the 90s--Pat Summerall and Wally Armstrong. WWOR-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 6:30 AM.
    - Psychic Friends Network. WWOR-TV. 1992 Mar. 28. 7:00 AM.